http://www.re-soft.com/privacy-statement

ReSoft privacy statement - | ReSoft
Search...
HomeWorkspace ManagementThe New Normal - Touchless Workspace and Room ManagementQUBI Workplace ManagementRoom Sign SolutionsResource and Room SchedulingReputation & Risk: Redact sensitive email content internally and at the perimeter:
Change Employee behavior to not click: Identify emerging phishing email threats earlier: Encrypt data-in-motion to protect E-Forms, email and ftpOffice 365 & MigrationLegacy Email
MigrationPST EliminationPubic Folder MigrationEmail Archive MigrationMonitor Office 365 SLA and uptimeEncrypted Email delivery for Office 365Mimecast for Office365ContactCompanyWhy You Need ReSoftCustomersRecent ProjectsBlog
Home  //
privacy Statement
Privacy Statement
ReSoft Privacy Policy
www.re-soft.com and www.resoftco.com is the web site of ReSoft International LLC. Our postal address is310 W 56th Street, #12ANew York NY 10019USA
We can be reached via e-mail by This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.
Or you can reach us by telephone at 203 972 8462.
For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes only the visitor's domain name, but not the e-mail address.
Should you decide to contact us, we will use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing future product sales offers for you, improving our services, and communicating with you.
If you supply us with your email address, your postal address and telephone number online you may receive periodic mailings, emails or telephone calls from us with information that we believe may be of interest to you regarding new products, services or upcoming specials.  If you do not wish to receive emails from us, please let us know in an email This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it..
We will not sell your email address or contact details to anyone.
If you do not wish to receive postal mailings or telephone calls from us, please let us know by mailing a letter containing your exact name and address to ReSoft International LLC at the above address.  We will promptly remove your addresses and telephone numbers from our lists.
Again, ReSoft International can be contacted at 203-972-8462 or This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it. to send email
Read the ReSoft Buyers Guide
Not sure?
203 972 8462
Our Customers
Recent Projects
Guidance on Sales Tax for Customers
Contact
Re-Soft today to get help!
To order products or request more information, click here or email This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it. detailing your requirements or call us at (203) 972-8462 to discuss your needs.
Blog
Tags
Domino Migration Exchange management Mobile Security Encryption PST Email Monitoring Office 365 Identity Governance Unified messaging EDiscovery Social media governance Electronic discovery request SharePoint Records retention
HomeProductsCustomersBlogContact UsPrivacy StatementSitemapSales Tax Reporting By State
Copyright © ReSoft International LLC 1997-2019. All rights reserved. All trademarks, servicemarks are respected. ReSoft International LLC · 310 W 56th St,  Suite 12A New York NY 10019 : Tel: 203 972 8462
Website by Square Squared
Scroll Up
